I'm Julie Branum.
Coming from utasana or standing forward fold, take a nice deep breath in and lengthen the chest up away from the thighs.
Good on your exhale bring your arms along side the body so hands are back by the hips and hold the posture.
On another inhale lift the chest up as you stand up tall swinging the arms up over head and exhale, place your hands at your heart center Now coming into this pose from trikanasana, step the right foot back, three and a half feet.
Left toe is pointing straight forward, right toes are at 45 degree angle.
Both legs are nice and straight.
Take a nice deep breath in as you extend those arms out away from the shoulders.
Exhale and lace the the left hand down on to the left shin swinging the right arm up to the sky.
This is a great time to use a block if needed.
If you feel that you have a little tightness and this is a little bit more of a lift, good.
Make sure the weight is in the front of the heel right where the heel and the foot come together so that the quadricep is lifted a little bit with the shin and the calf action.
Good.
Extend and lengthen on every inhale.
On every exhale hugging in muscularly the legs with the quadriceps, the calves and the shin muscles.
Beautiful.
Another deep breath in holding as you lengthen and exhale.
Finish and fold that right hand back down to the floor.
Great job Valerie and Linda.
Wonderful.